inpixio.com 2017-06-06

# InPixio Privacy Policy

InPixio is part of Softcity, an entity of the Avanquest Group.

Are you concerned about your privacy? Doing business together requires some sharing of information. Set out below is our Privacy Policy, explaining what information we collect and why, what we do with it and how we protect you.

### Registration, download and purchase

To access certain areas of the InPixio.com or SoftCity.com website (especially to download or to buy), you will first be asked to complete a form to either download a trial version, a free software title, or to create an account before buying any of our products.

#### Registration

During registration, you may be required to provide your contact information, such as your name, email address, postal address, payment information and to choose a password. Your email address is your username. We send all newly registered users a welcoming email to verify their password and username.

It’s very important that you submit a working email address because that is where we’ll send your purchase confirmation, download links, activation keys, support and product notices.

#### Purchase

When buying a product on the site, you will be asked for your contact details and billing and, if applicable, shipping information. This data will be used to process the order, to get the payment through the credit card verification process, and to ship any item(s) you ordered. If there is a problem with the order, a SoftCity representative may contact you by email. A confirmation email is sent for each purchase to the address you give us – so if you have a few addresses take a moment to remember which one you give us.

#### Download

When downloading a trial version or a free software program, you will be asked for contact information, including your email address. You will receive email messages related to this transaction such as to provide you with download links, activation keys, support notices and upgrades for the software.

### Surveys and contests

From time to time, we request information from SoftCity.com users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary. This information is mainly used to better understand our audience and to send prizes to the winners when needed. Should the results of a contest or a survey be published, no personal information will be divulged without the explicit consent of the winners.

### Your subscription to SoftCity Newsletters and Special Offers

When submitting your email address, you are given the opportunity to “opt-in” to the SoftCity newsletter. By opting to receive this communication, SoftCity will send you regular emails containing relevant product and service information, new product and upgrade information, and any special offers that we think may be relevant to you.

### If you wish to unsubscribe from the newsletter

If at any time you wish to opt-out from these communications, please follow the unsubscribe link contained in the emails, or email us with your request to be removed from our mailing list.

When you officially “unsubscribe” through our links or site we commit to remove the email address from our mailing lists as soon as possible, and usually before the next mailing. From that point you will no longer receive our newsletters or special offers. However, please take note that if you purchased software or downloaded trial versions in the past or if you decide to purchase or download a trial version again after you’ve unsubscribed, we may still send you service emails directly related to these transactions, such as order confirmations, product notices, expiry notifications, bug fix notifications, security alerts, compatibility notifications, or enhancements.

### No sharing of information to preserve your privacy

SoftCity is the sole owner of information collected on its websites. We will not sell, disclose, or rent this information to others except if required to by contract or through a legal proceeding or law.

We may share aggregated information with our partners and advertisers. However, this information is not linked to any personally identifiable information. SoftCity carefully reviews the privacy policies of partners, affiliates and subsidiaries to ensure that they reflect the same attention and commitment to privacy as SoftCity.com

### When visiting other websites, you’re on your own.

Our website may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

### Using cookies for statistical and analytical purposes – ultimately, it’s all about improving your experience on our site.

SoftCity.com website uses cookies. Cookies are small pieces of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser.

The SoftCity website does not collect any personal information from cookies. They are used to make the login process easier for our users, to allow the website to track which products you have added to your basket and your preferred country, language and currency, and to track broad user movements for statistical purposes.

If you do not want your personal information to be stored by cookies, you can alter the settings in your browser so that it alters you whenever a cookie is received. You can then decide if you wish to accept them or not on a case by case basis. Please be aware that the use of cookies may be required to provide certain features and deciding to reject cookies may negatively impact the functionality of the site. Your browser help tab should include detailed instructions outlining how to handle cookies.

### 3rd Party Cookies

SoftCity may also employ third party vendors, including Google to show our ads on sites on the internet and to use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website. These cookies do not store sensitive information such as contact details. At any time, users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

From time to time, we may also use Remarketing Dynamic Ads which use the Teracent cookie. Users may opt out of the Teracent cookie by visiting the [Teracent opt-out page](http://www.teracent.com/about-us/opt-out/).

We may also use DoubleClick Remarketing PIxels. Users may opt out of DoubleClick’s use of cookies by visiting Teracent cookie by visiting the [DoubleClick opt-out page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb#display_optout) or the[Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All the data regarding customers, users, their computers’ system information and data are stored on a server. This server is located in a locked and guarded space and only authorized personnel have access to the database containing the stored information.

### Notification of Changes

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our site. If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users via email. Users will be able to opt out of any new use of their personal information.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, the practices of our sites, or your dealings with any of our websites, you can contact [support@softcity.com](mailto:support@softcity.com)
